Guide to the Whirlwind Hill Farm Papers (1940-1977)
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Business Records and Documents, Series VII
  - Cattle
    - Talk on purebreds by JMO. Notes and draft copies. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Cattle certificates. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Cow family data. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Bull inquiry letters. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Farm finance and related items
    - Farm - anticipated income and expenses., 1940-48. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Farm accounts. 1940-47. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Farm accounts. 1945-49. (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Farm accounts. 1950. (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Farm accounts. 1953. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Farm accounts. 1954. (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Farm accounts. 1958. (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Farm accounts. 1959. (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Farm taxes. 1955. (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Farm correspondence. (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Farmhouse. 1940. (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Farm equipment. 1940-41. (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Farm underground tank. 1948. (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Farm - barn repairs and contract. 1956-57. (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - George W. Cooke, COAG Farm, Inc. 1962. (Box 11, Folder 30)
      Correspondence between Mr. Cooke and Mr. Osborn
      about pond.
    - Farm - JMO's reply to New Haven Register advertisements. (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Farm - sale of property. 1965. (Box 11, Folder 32)
      Accompanied by letter from Peter Powers
      Hale to JMO.
    - Farm - geography. (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Farm - miscellaneous. (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Federal Land Bank. 1941-49. (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Leighton Gibbs Account. 1958-60. (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Bronson, Rice and Lyman, attorneys. 1940-42. (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Farm insurance - Thompson and Peck. 1957. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Farm insurance - Clifford Heilig. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Farm insurance - miscellaneous. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Household Social Security. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Blue Cross of Connecticut. 1943-56. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Blue Cross of Connecticut. 1957-69. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Receipt book. Loose-leaf pages for miscellaneous accounts. 1942-51. (Box 12, Folder 7)